swebie.com 2015-06-13

# Privacy-policy|Free Kids Games|Free Girls Games at Swebie

#### Swebie Privacy Policy

Swebie has designed its privacy policy to impart users about the types of information that the site collects and usage of such information. Swebie reserves rights to make amendments in the privacy policy, when needs arise. Users are recommended to keep themselves well informed about the changes by periodical visits to the privacy policy webpage. By using the website, you agree with Swebie’s privacy policy and in case you do not, please stop using the site. No correspondence or arguments are entertained on this regard. 

#### Collection and Use of User Information

Swebie maintains a demographic database of its users, for which purpose the site collects user IPs. Swebie drops cookies on browsers to track the page views and downloads of the user. Such non personally identifiable information are used to provide advertisements of products and services that relate to the customer in a better way. 

Swebie might also collect personally identifiable information such as name, password, date of birth and email address with complete consent of the users. Such details are used to communicate with the users in the form of newsletters, requests, greetings and so on. Such personally identifiable information is kept confidential and is not shared with third parties.

#### IP Address, Cookies and Web Beacons

Swebie drops cookies, web beacons and other new technologies in your browser to track your browsing habits. Such information is used to measure advertisement effects and is implemented to enhance more appropriate communications. Cookies are stored in your local computer and collect user name, current date and time. 

Your IP address information is kept confidential and could be disclosed only for legal purposes, when Swebie chooses to defend its property and rights.

Web beacons or web bugs are used by websites that use third party web traffic monitoring services. The transparent image file is used to track your journey through a website or series of websites. 

#### Third Party Sponsors

Users at Swebie might be exposed to advertisements from partner sites and third party advertising companies. Such organizations use non-personally identifiable information such as Internet Service Provider (ISP), browser type, software and hardware details of the user’s computer or mobile instruments. Based on such information the third party advertisers may serve targeted advertisements about products and services that sync well with the viewer’s needs.

#### Third Party Cookies

While you browse advertisements at Swebie, you witness third party advertisers dropping their cookies at your browser. Such tracking is used to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements.

#### Conclusion

So much so, for the privacy policy that Swebie adapts. Enjoy the games at Swebie and have unlimited fun. Thank You.
